(this["webpackJsonpquiz-app"]=this["webpackJsonpquiz-app"]||[]).push([[0],{11:function(e,t,s){"use strict";s.r(t);var r=s(1),n=s.n(r),i=s(4),o=s.n(i),a=(s(9),s(2)),c=s(0);function T(){var e=[{questionText:"What does HTML stand for?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Hyper Text Markup Language",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Home Tool Markup Language",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"None of these",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"The correct sequence of HTML tags for starting a webpage is ",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Head, Title, HTML, body",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"HTML, Body, Title, Head",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"HTML, Head, Title, Body",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"HTML, Head, Title, Body",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"How to create a checkbox in HTML?",answerOptions:[{answerText:'<input type = "checkbox">',isCorrect:!0},{answerText:'<input type = "button">',isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"<checkbox>",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:'<input type = "check">',isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"HTML tags are enclosed in-",answerOptions:[{answerText:"# and #",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"{ and }",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"{ and }",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"< and >",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"Which of the following attribute is used to provide a unique name to an element?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"class",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"id",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"type",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"None of the above",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Which of the following is the correct way to send mail in HTML?",answerOptions:[{answerText:'<a href = "mailto: xy@y">',isCorrect:!0},{answerText:'<a href = "xy@y">',isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"<mail xy@y</mail>",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"None of the above",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Which of the following HTML attribute is used to define inline styles?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"style",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"type",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"class",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"None of the above",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"The tags in HTML are -",answerOptions:[{answerText:"case-sensitive",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"in upper case",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"not case sensitive",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"in lowercase",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Which of the following is the root tag of the HTML document?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"<body>",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"<head>",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"<title>",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"<html>",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:" In HTML5, which of the following tag is used to initialize the document type?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"<Doctype HTML>",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"<Doctype html>",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"<Doctype>",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"<!DOCTYPE html>",isCorrect:!0}]}],t=Object(r.useState)(0),s=Object(a.a)(t,2),n=s[0],i=s[1],o=Object(r.useState)(!1),T=Object(a.a)(o,2),x=T[0],w=T[1],u=Object(r.useState)(0),l=Object(a.a)(u,2),h=l[0],d=l[1];return Object(c.jsx)("div",{className:"app",children:x?Object(c.jsx)("div",{className:"score-section",children:Object(c.jsxs)("h2",{children:[h>=5?"\ud83d\ude0e":"\ud83d\ude22"," You scored ",h," out of ",e.length," ",h>=5?"\ud83d\ude0e":"\ud83d\ude22"]})}):Object(c.jsxs)(c.Fragment,{children:[Object(c.jsxs)("div",{className:"question-section",children:[Object(c.jsxs)("div",{className:"question-count",children:[Object(c.jsxs)("span",{children:[" Question ",n+1]}),"/",e.length," :",Object(c.jsx)("hr",{})]}),Object(c.jsx)("div",{className:"question-text",children:Object(c.jsx)("b",{children:e[n].questionText})})]}),Object(c.jsx)("div",{className:"answer-section",children:e[n].answerOptions.map((function(t){return Object(c.jsx)("button",{onClick:function(){return function(t){t&&d(h+1);var s=n+1;s<e.length?i(s):w(!0)}(t.isCorrect)},children:t.answerText})}))})]})})}var x=function(e){e&&e instanceof Function&&s.e(3).then(s.bind(null,12)).then((function(t){var s=t.getCLS,r=t.getFID,n=t.getFCP,i=t.getLCP,o=t.getTTFB;s(e),r(e),n(e),i(e),o(e)}))};o.a.render(Object(c.jsxs)(n.a.StrictMode,{children:[Object(c.jsx)("h1",{style:{textAlign:"center"},children:"Quiz App\ud83d\udcad "}),Object(c.jsx)(T,{})]}),document.getElementById("root")),x()},9:function(e,t,s){}},[[11,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.234d7d25.chunk.js.map